visainfoservices.com 2016-11-28

# WorldBridge Visa Information

Return to WorldBridge homepage

This privacy statement regarding Customer and online user information applies to Computer Sciences Corporation and its worldwide corporate affiliates (“we” or “our”) but not to those Computer Sciences Corporation affiliates that have published their own privacy statements. This privacy statement also does not apply to the websites of our business partners or to any other third parties, even if their websites are linked to our website. We recommend you review the privacy statements of the other parties with whom you interact.

This statement describes the types of personal data collected by us, where they are stored, how they are protected and who will have access to them and why. By clicking the submit button during your transaction, you acknowledge you have read and understood this privacy statement and agree to the collection, use, disclosure, and disposition of your personal data as described below.

We respect your right to privacy. You are invited to search or browse the site without revealing who you are or registering with us. There are times, however, that you may choose to use the interactive functions of this site to provide us Personal information, for example, to order documents or to initiate services. This policy states how we will use and protect such Personal information, it does not and is not intended to create any contractual or other legal rights.

For the purposes of this privacy statement, “corporate affiliates” means any entity or joint venture that is wholly or partially owned by Computer Sciences Corporation. “Personal information” means any information which identifies you, such as your name, telephone number and email address. “Business Partners” means any subcontractor, vendor or other entity with whom we have an ongoing business relationship to provide products, services or information.

If you choose to visit www.visainfoservices.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Statement, our Website Use Terms, and Conditions of Sale.

## Information we collect

We may ask you to provide Personal information when you:

  * Use our website 
  * Request services, support or information 
  * Place orders for products or services 
  * Contact us

Information we may request includes your email address, name, home address and telephone number. We may collect information about your visits to our websites, including the pages you view, the link and ads you click, and other actions you take in connection with our website and services. We may also collect certain information from the browser you used to come to our website such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, language, access times, the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) of the website that referred you to our website and to which URL you browse away from our site if you click on a link on our site.

Some of our services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If you register for or use such services, both CSC and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services, and may use the information according to each company’s privacy statement and other agreements with you.

## How we use Personal information

CSC uses your Personal information to:

  * Deliver the services or carry out, the transactions you have requested; 
  * Send communications to you, such as your transaction status 
  * Customize, analyze, and improve our products, services (including the content and advertisements on our website), technologies, communications and relationship with you; 
  * Enforce our conditions of sale, website use terms and/or separate contracts (if applicable) with you; 
  * Prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities; 
  * Protect the security or integrity of the website, our business, or our products or services; or 
  * Otherwise, as disclosed to you at the point of collection

Personal information collected may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which CSC or its corporate affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using CSC products or services (including www.visainfoservices.com), you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. CSC will not sell, distribute or disclose your Personal information to any third party except with your express prior consent or unless legally compelled to disclose by court order or other legal process. In the latter case, we will endeavour to contact you with information prior to disclosure to enable you to object to such disclosure.

## How we secure your Personal information

CSC is committed to protecting the security of your Personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure, such as encryption, passwords, physical security, etc. While we strive to protect your Personal information, CSC cannot ensure or warrant that the Personal information or private communications you transmit to us will always remain private, and you do so at your own risk.

## Disclosing Personal information

We may share your Personal information with corporate affiliates to carry out transactions you request or to make our business or that of our corporate affiliates more responsive to your needs. We may also disclose your Personal information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, or other legal action; as required by law or regulation; or if we reasonably believe it is necessary to protect CSC, its customers, or the public. In addition, we may share your Personal information with Business Partners that help CSC carry out transactions you request or that help CSC to customize, analyze, and/or improve our communication or relationship with you, and then only with Business Partners who share CSC's commitment to protecting your Personal information. Except as described above, we will not disclose your Personal information to third parties for their own marketing purposes unless you have provided consent.

## Collection and Use of Children's Personal Information

CSC takes children's privacy seriously. We do not knowingly collect Personal information from children under the age of 13 through our websites. If you are under 18 years of age, please do not submit any Personal information through our websites without the express consent and participation of a parent or guardian.

## Third-Party Websites and Services

Please be aware that other websites that may be accessed through our website may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those third-party websites linked to [www.visainfoservices.com](http://www.visainfoservices.com/) are not covered by this privacy statement. 

Please be aware that, in providing services on CSC’s behalf, our Business Partners may collect Personal information about you.

## Online Payment Card Transactions

You may purchase products or services via the online payment facility. When submitting your payment details, you will enter all cardholder data fields into a third party payment module, hosted by WorldPay Ltd. WorldPay Ltd are acting as the data processor on behalf of CSC. By submitting your payment details online, you provide your consent to the transfer of your cardholder details and billing address direct to WorldPay Ltd for the processing of the payment data and transaction authorization. 

This privacy statement does not apply to the services of WorldPay Ltd or to any other third parties, even if their websites are linked to our website. We recommend you review the privacy statements of WorldPay Ltd or any other parties with whom you interact.

## Cookies

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard disk so that the website can remember who you are. The WorldBridge website does not use cookies to store information on your computer.

## Changes to Our Privacy Statement Regarding Customer and Online User Information

We will occasionally update this privacy statement. If we make changes to the Privacy Statement regarding Customer and Online User Information or make any material changes to how CSC will use your Personal information, we will revise the Privacy Statement to reflect such changes and revise the statement's effective date, included at the end of this section. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how CSC is protecting your Personal information.

## Contact

Please contact CSC, Royal Pavilion, Wellesley Road, Aldershot, Hampshire, GU11 1PZ, United Kingdom if you have any questions about the collection and processing of your information by CSC. If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, please select the country from where you are travelling on the www.visainfoservices.com homepage. On the menu on the left select the Send an Email Enquiry or Suggestion option and submit your enquiries.

Return to WorldBridge homepage
